<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Trab</string>
    <string name="name">IPVC MAPS</string>
    <!--><string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <!-->
    <string name="mapa_entrar">See Map</string>
    <string name="empresas">See companies</string>
    <string name="foot1">Privacy Policy – Privacy E Terms</string>
    <string name="policies">
        <![CDATA[


        <b>Privacy Policy</b><br/>
        At IPVC MAPS, we are committed to protecting your privacy. This policy outlines how we collect, use, and share information to improve your experience with our app.<br/><br/>

        <b>Information Collection:</b><br/>
        We may collect personal details like your name and email when you use our app, as well as device data, IP address, and usage patterns to enhance app performance.<br/><br/>

        <b>Usage of Information:</b><br/>
        Information is used to provide, personalize, and improve our services, communicate with you, and for analytics purposes.<br/><br/>

        <b>Data Sharing:</b><br/>
        We only share information with trusted third-party providers essential for operating our service or as required by law.<br/><br/>

        <b>Security:</b><br/>
        We apply standard security practices to protect your data but note that no method is 100% secure.<br/><br/>

        <b>User Rights:</b><br/>
        You have rights to access, correct, or delete your personal data. Contact us if you wish to exercise these rights.<br/><br/>

        <b>Terms of Service</b><br/><br/>

        <b>Usage:</b><br/>
        Use the app lawfully and respectfully. Unauthorized use or abuse of our service may lead to restrictions on your account.<br/><br/>

        <b>Account Responsibility:</b><br/>
        You are responsible for safeguarding your account credentials and any activity under your account.<br/><br/>

        <b>Intellectual Property:</b><br/>
        All app content is owned by IPVC MAPS and is protected under intellectual property laws.<br/><br/>

        <b>Limitation of Liability:</b><br/>
        IPVC MAPS is not liable for any damages or losses arising from the use of our app.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="iniciar_ses">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="pass">Password</string>
    <string name="nao_conta">Don\'t have an account? Create it here</string>
    <string name="create_acc">SIGN-UP</string>
    <string name="conf_pass">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="have_acc">Already have an account? Log in here</string>
    <string name="pesquisa">Search Here</string>
    <string name="saber">More</string>
</resources>